# **Tetia**na Panasiuk

Frontend Developer

Phone

**Email** 

+48575277368

tetianapanasiuk93@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tetiana-panasiuk/

### **Address**

### **Profile**

#### Cracow



#### About me

I am a Frontend Developer with over 4 years of commercial experience, specializing in building modern, responsive, and accessible websites. I transform designs into high-performance and pixel-perfect websites using the latest technologies, following a mobile-first approach and accessibility guidelines.

#### Skills

JavaScript, React/Redux, jQuery, HTML/HTML5, CSS/CSS3, REST API, Vitest, Jest, Bootstrap, Less/SASS/SCSS, Git/GitHub, Figma, Atlassian (Jira, Bitbucket, Confluence), CI/CD, Jenkins, Agile (Scrum).

## Experience

# **SmartRecruiters**

05.2024 - now

Web Developer Cracow

- Creating and optimizing web-components following mobile-first approach and accessibility guidelines (HTML5, CSS/SCSS), JavaScript, TypeScript, React)
- Developing career websites for company's customers based on Figma designs, ensuring accurate implementation of layouts, typography and design components
- Following code quality standards: unit tests (Vitest, Jest), code review.

## Cornerstone OnDemand

08.2022 - 04.2024 (1y 9m)

Software Engineer Cracow

- Developing front end for customized login page management application (React/Redux, TypeScript)
- Developing the tool for managing branding specification requirements (Vue.js, Less)
- Creating custom branded web components based on customers' requirements and mock-ups (HTML, CSS, lavaScript)
- · Customization of customers' career websites and extending their functionality (JavaScript, jQuery)

## Saba Software

01.2019 - 07.2020 (1y 7m)

Junior Front Office Developer Cracow

- Configuring the recruitment platform and delivering JavaScript based components, incl. "look'n'feel" modifications (CSS, HTML, Bootstrap)
- Integrating customers' job applications to web pages and WordPress CMS, configuring and styling this
  according to branding guidelines (WordPress, CSS)

# Arvato Finance

02.2017 - 08.2018 (1y 6m)

Customer Service Representative Cracow

- Providing high quality online customer service related to Google Ads, Google Analytics, Google Tag Manager etc.)
- Planning and maintaining the team schedule to make sure the workflow is followed
- Reporting the overall team performance on a daily basis and creating weekly reports

Education

Taras Shevchenko National University Of Kyiv

Master Of Arts: English Language, Ukrainian Language, Literature

English (Advanced)

Polish (Advanced)

Ukrainian (Native)

Work permit

Not needed